So friends, as you all
are currently connected to our channel, you all know that
I am
not making videos for quite some time now, so now I am back for you again with a
new video,
with a new product, our new product is
ICC Prudential's Protected, there is going to be
something very special in this product
for you, this product has just been launched on 29th June, in which
I will tell you the special things in the video, so let's go
friends and hello friends,
welcome to our channel, as you
all know, if you are new to our channel, then
subscribe to the channel,
like the video and share it, don't be
fooled, your share and like increases our motivation
and we keep bringing new videos like this, so
friends, today we will talk about
this special product Protest Time
Game, what is special in it, let me tell you, from the
name of Protest Game itself you must have understood,
means you have to get the protection ball of protest, so till now the
product of ICC Prudential was
iProtest Smart and iProtest Return
of Premium, so return of premium
premium was available, something like this, I will tell you about it  I
will explain the video in detail, so
what is going to be special in this video, till now if
you had to take any term plan then it was
mandatory that your post
graduation should be complete,
yes, so what was special in that video, the special thing about that
product was that in it your
post graduation or graduation was mandatory that
below graduation, that policy will not be available,
if you are a businessman then you should have an ITR of 5 lakhs
and if you are salaried then
your salary slip etc. all these things are
required in it, there was nothing for housewives who have passed 10th or anything below below the
level,
so
what is special in this product, if we talk about educational qualification
then if she is even high school passed then the
product can be given to her,
she can take protection on her own
and along with the protection, she can
also take a plan like ULIP, apart from this, if
we talk about it then if a housewife is
not doing any work then she can also take it, a
student can also take it, all the
special features are given in it  So now we
move towards this product, let us tell
you that the premium in this product of ours is
minimum 5 years
and maximum 12 years i.e. 5, 6, 7, 9, 10, 11, 12.
All the options are available to you that you can earn
any PPT i.e. premium from 5 to 12 years.
Apart from this, if we talk about
how long the PT is live in this, how long is the policy term, then
this policy term is minimum 30 years and
maximum 40 years. You can take Current S
Plus 30 or Current S Plus maximum 14, so
this is PPT and PPT. Now if we
talk about it, the minimum coverage we get,
which we know as Life Is Short, till now, if
we used to go for any product, if we used to
go for any company product,
there we used to get minimum 25 lakhs and
maximum up to 1 crore. If
we talk about this product, then in this you will
get minimum 50 lakhs and maximum ₹1 crore, this is it.  Talking about life cover, along with this
you will get life benefit as well as
accidental benefit plus accidental death,
if there is death benefit due to accident then you will
get it, if you get permanent
disabilities or normal
disabilities due to accident then also you will get a minimum benefit of Rs. 50 lakh
and a maximum benefit of Rs. 1 crore,
in this you will get these two riders in plus, that is
accidental death benefit plus and
accidental disability benefit is also plus, so in this
if you have
bought a plane, for example, you have bought a plane worth Rs. 50 lakh
and you are going on the road,
you have an accident and what happens due to your accident is that you get
disabled, you are put on
bed rest for six months, a year or two years, the
doctor writes that brother, now he
cannot do anything for 1-2 years, he
needs proper bed rest for 2 years, so
what will happen in that condition that the person who has been
disabled due to accident, that is 50
lakh, that 50 lakh will be given to you  It will be given to you, with that
you can treat your illness,
manage your household expenses, your family
expenses and you
can also pay your premium. Yes
friends, this option has definitely been given in this that in case of
disability, you will get ₹50 lakhs
but along with that, your previous
policy will continue. Now, in this
you can take 50 lakhs, easily you can manage your household expenses,
family expenses, children's education or your
premium expenses, whatever it is.
50 lakhs is a big amount for 2 years, it is
not a small amount.
Suppose there is no disability,
someone dies due to an accident,
whoever is the policy holder, then his nominee will be paid
₹50 lakh accidental benefit plus 50 lakhs, that is, a
total amount of ₹1 crore,
whichever was the name of the policy holder. So,
friends, this was the life benefit, accident benefit
plus accidental disability tax. So,
you must have seen the incidents in case of accidental disability.  It has become common that we are
going by car or bike, we meet with an accident
and get disabled in the road accident,
now we will be able to walk after two months, our body parts are broken and our
hand is broken, we cannot go back, we
cannot run our business, we are sitting at home, so
what happens to that, brother,
who will run our house in our absence, if we become disabled,
who will bear our expenses, our
expenses will remain on our policy, this will
give us 50 lakhs on going digital, here
friends, we are getting minimum 50 lakhs, so
now this 50 lakhs will be ours, whatever we do with it,
our policy is continuing, even
after that if anything happens to the policy holder, for example, if
he dies due to an
accident, then he will get one crore, if he
dies normally, then he will get 50 lakhs, now this is done in
life insurance, now if there is a fraud in the policy,
like there is a fraud in the policy
after 60, you can take it, right now it is for 30 years,
take it for 33 years or 30 years, so
we have given it to you, the company has given it to you
in this product  The tax period is 40 years, the maximum and
minimum is 30 years, you have taken 30 years, now
what happens on the tax period of 30 years is that
after taking tax for 30 years, you were still in peace, you took
tax for the next 30 years, you turned 60 years old, as soon as the
policy ended, you turned 60 years old, you get
an amount between 40 to 50 lakhs,
which we call lump sum amount,
what do we do with this amount, we
invest it in the fund through ULIP, now in this
you have to do any fund thing, whatever fund
thing you do or whoever is your agent, or
whatever bank you are taking it from, or ICC bank, or
any bank, then
whoever is doing any one of your policies there is an
agent, he will
invest your money in any fund,
whatever fund will be running in the market, 10%, 15%, or
20% or early, then the money that you get from it,
you will get it on the maturity of the policy, now
what happened in this, we got the tax of the life,
Whatever we did for a minimum maximum of 40 years,
along with that,
what happened to us was that we also got a game in the manner of ULIP, at the
market price, whatever the market
rate is, what happened to us at that rate,
30 lakh, 40 lakh, 50 lakh, whatever amount we have taken,
we will get it. Now it comes to the premium on this,
if you have taken a loan for 30 lakhs for 30
years and
you have taken a loan of 50 lakhs, then your premium on the loan of one lakh will be
something like this, 60000, 50 thousand,
you did it for 10 years, then you gave ₹6 lakhs to the
company, you paid ₹6 lakhs to the potential,
now by paying 6 lakhs,
you are getting a
life tax of ₹50 crores, yes friends, death benefit of ₹50 lakhs,
accidental death benefit of ₹50 lakhs,
you also get ₹50 lakhs on accidental permanent disability or
normal disability and you will get
₹50 lakhs  The total live score is going to be received,
plus tax of 2 lakhs, as long as we have kept the tax for
30 years, as soon as 30 years are completed,
what happens on the last 30 years is that
we get 40 lakhs amount,
friends, how much did we pay,
₹6 lakhs, how much did we get, 40 lakh rupees, so this
40 lakh rupees will also be ours, the live tax will
also be ours and there will be laughter and happiness live too,
now with this we are getting ATC benefit up to 2 lakhs,
plus this maturity
amount of 40 lakhs that you are getting, if you take a deposit from the story, take a deposit
in FB,
take a deposit in RD, take a deposit in PF, then
you have to pay tax to the government,
but in this plan you do
not have to pay any tax according to 10-20%
security, the total lumpsum amount will be
tax free for you, now along with this maturity amount
being tax free, you are
also getting a live tax of 2 crores, that means
4 benefits from one plan  Income of lakhs
after 30 years Life tax of crores
Tax benefit of 10 lakhs in 10 years
Tax benefit from ₹1 to ₹1.5 lakh Apart from this,
we got any benefit,
got benefit of 10-20 years Life tax along with lump sum
amount So one plan and 4 benefits
Friends, we have got tax benefit with one plan
here, so no
plan has come in the market till now, due to which
we can get such good maturity
in such a small account, it is not possible, so
friends, you should also think about this plan,
you should also think about your life,
when you are doing salary, then you
can also take it, it is not an amount for you,
60000 rupees early, if you look at it,
basically you will get 5000 rupees monthly, you pack ₹5000
monthly and you will get an amount of 40 lakhs
after 30 years, now your 30 years will be
ahead of you  30 years as soon as you retire,
after retirement you
get a cool amount of ₹40000, along with that
during the 30 years of life period you
get a live tax of up to Rs. 1.5 lakh, so here you
also keep yourself fit, you are
taking the ball and doing something for the family as well
or even if you are not doing anything,
you are getting the benefit of that plan even while you are alive, so
friends this was
our plan, how did you like it, do
tell us in the comments, we will meet
in the next video, till then Jai Hind